# This file should contain all the record creation needed to seed the database with its default values.
# The data can then be loaded with the rails db:seed command (or created alongside the database with db:setup).
#
# Examples:
#
#   movies = Movie.create([{ name: 'Star Wars' }, { name: 'Lord of the Rings' }])
#   Character.create(name: 'Luke', movie: movies.first)

require 'faker'

5.times do
user = {:username => Faker::Internet.user_name, :email => Faker::Internet.safe_email, :password => 'password'}

 User.create!(user)
end

# Deck.create(:name => "Life Questions")
# # DECK 1
# Card.create(question: "Is Pat kind?", answer: "Yes", deck_id: 1)
# Card.create(question: "Is Mitch tall?", answer: "Yes", deck_id: 1)
# Card.create(question: "Are rainbows special?", answer: "No" , deck_id: 1)
# Card.create(question: "You hungry?", answer: "Yes", deck_id: 1)
# Card.create(question: "Is ghost pepper salsa tasty as fuck?", answer: "Yes", deck_id: 1)
# Card.create(question: "Are DBC students caffienated?", answer: "Yes", deck_id: 1)


# Deck.create(:name => "Sour Patch Kids")
# # DECK 2
# Card.create(question: "Which color SPK is best SPK color?", answer: "Yellow", deck_id: 2)
# Card.create(question: "When did God create SPKs?", answer: "1970", deck_id: 2)
# Card.create(question: "Is there tartaric acid in SPKs?", answer: "Yes", deck_id: 2)
# Card.create(question: "How many SPKs does it take to reach Nirvana?", answer: "Just One", deck_id: 2)
# Card.create(question: "Are there any health drawbacks to consuming SPKs?", answer: "No", deck_id: 2)
# Card.create(question: "If a person offers you either one SPK now, or two SPKs in an hour, what should you do?", answer: "Forcibly Take All Three.", deck_id: 2)
# Card.create(question: "If you mix Swedish Fish with SPKs, do you now possess an improved version of trail mix?", answer: "Yes", deck_id: 2)

# Deck.create(name: "Pac-Man Ghosts")
# # DECK 3
# Card.create(question: "Which Pac-Man ghost is red?", answer: "Blinky", deck_id: 3)
# Card.create(question: "Which Pac-Man ghost is pink?", answer: "Pinky", deck_id: 3)
# Card.create(question: "Which Pac-Man ghost is blue?", answer: "Inky", deck_id: 3)
# Card.create(question: "Which Pac-Man ghost is orange?", answer: "Clyde", deck_id: 3)
# Card.create(question: "What is the 'character' description of Blinky's chasing style?", answer: "Shadow", deck_id: 3)
# Card.create(question: "What is the 'character' description of Pinky's chasing style?", answer: "Speedy", deck_id: 3)
# Card.create(question: "What is the 'character' description of Inky's chasing style?", answer: "Bashful", deck_id: 3)
# Card.create(question: "What is the 'character' description of Clyde's chasing style?", answer: "Pokey", deck_id: 3)
# Card.create(question: "True or False: Each ghost behaves according to its own unique algorithm?", answer: "True", deck_id: 3)
# Card.create(question: "How many points are awarded for gobbling up all four ghosts?", answer: "1600", deck_id: 3)



# Deck.create(name: "Pac-Man Factoids")
# # DECK 4
# Card.create(question: "How many points are awarded for eating a strawberry?", answer: "300", deck_id: 4)
# Card.create(question: "True or False: Pac-Man moves slower while eating pellets?", answer: "True", deck_id: 4)
# Card.create(question: "What year was Pac-Man released?", answer: "1980", deck_id: 4)
# Card.create(question: "The things Pac-Man eats are referred to as pellets. What is the 'official' name for them?", answer: "Pac-Dots", deck_id: 4)
# Card.create(question: "Which level is unplayable due to integer overflow?", answer: "456", deck_id: 4)
# Card.create(question: "Which Japanese company developed Pac-Man", answer: "Namco", deck_id: 4)
# Card.create(question: "Is it a good idea to always keep 45-cents in your pocket in case you encounter a Pac-Man game?", answer: "Yes", deck_id: 4)
# Card.create(question: "To get this question correct, do a Pac-Man impression and type 'Impression Complete'.", answer: "Impression Complete", deck_id: 4)
# Card.create(question: "The original name was Puck-Man, but kids everywhere would've obviously vandalized every arcade cabinet to read:", answer: "Fuck-Man", deck_id: 4)